# RENE PRINCE

### CONTACT INFORMATION

Address: 70 Distillery Lane, Toronto Email: reneprince93@icloud.com

**Mobile:** 43-7227-3781

### **KEY SKILLS**

### Written and verbal communication skills –

strengthened by essays and presentations as part of my degree and work experience.

Excellent I.T skills – I can pick up how to use software quickly. I already have an extensive knowledge of the MS office suite.

Sport – I have a real passion for sport and have previously played professionally for QPR FC where I learnt valuable life lessons such as performing well under pressure and paying close attention to detail when completing a task

### **EDUCATION**

### 2012 - 2016

#### **Bournemouth University:**

BA Hons (2:1) Sport and Business Management

#### 2010 - 2012

### St. James Catholic High School (6<sup>th</sup> Form):

A-Levels: Physical Education (B); Business Studies (B); Statistics (C).

#### 2005 - 2010

#### St. James Catholic High School:

GCSEs: 10 A-C grades.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## December 2016 – August 2018 – We Are Tea Ltd Supply Chain and Business Development Manager

- Purchasing Buying raw materials and negotiating prices based on quantity and seasonal changes.
- Production Forecasting Analysing sales data and forecasting the demand for the future months to ensure accurate stock levels.
- Inbound Sales Dealing with new sales inquiries and upselling packages based on client needs.
- Project Management Managing new product launches and ensuring the project is executed to meet required deadlines.
- Logistics Management Managing a variety of different shipping methods and guaranteeing the quickest and most cost-effective method is chosen.
   Daily contact with distribution warehouse and ensuring customers are receiving deliveries on time. Processing incoming customer orders and make sure they are delivered on time.
- Customer Service Management Dealing with customer complaints and ensuring they are dealt with in a professional and timely manner.
- Account Management Managing relationships with key accounts and making sure they are organised and happy with the product.

### July 2016 – November 2016 – Lucozade Powerleague *Operations and Sales Coordinator*

- Operations Management Organise and lead corporate soccer tournaments from start to finish. Sourcing locations to hold events based on territory and ensuring customer needs are met.
- Sales Sourcing corporate teams' through cold and warm leads. Cold calling potential companies that would be suitable for the tournament.
   Contacting companies that have previously taken part in similar activities.
- Database Management Entering bookings into a database for tournaments, league matches and social bookings and maintaining a log of corporate contacts for future tournaments.

### September 2014 – August 2015 – Teddy Tennis Business Development and Operations Intern

- Competitor Analysis Reviewing competition and external factors to develop and improve the Teddy Tennis business.
- Client Liaison Interacting with current and potential clients ensuring they are organised and happy with the Teddy Tennis product.
- Marketing Advertising the product on social media and in schools, creating innovative methods to pitch to potential clients.
- Coaching Learning to deliver professional Teddy Tennis lessons.
- Calendar Management Plan and create client rota's to ensure the Teddy Tennis product is delivered.

August 2012 – September 2015 – IVS Group Limited Wembley Stadium Stand Leader